<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Latest Job Vacancies at Djinni</title>
        <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/</link>
        <description>Stay updated with the newest job opportunities at Djinni.</description>
        <atom:link href="https://djinni.co/jobs/rss/" rel="self"/>
        <language>uk</language>
        <category>Business Analyst</category>
        <category>ERP</category>
        <category>Android</category>
        <category>React.js</category>
        <category>Svelte</category>
        <category>Product Owner</category>
        <category>DevOps</category>
        <category>CMO</category>
        <category>2D Artist</category>
        <category>UX Research</category>
        <category>CFO</category>
        <category>Other</category>
        <category>UI UX</category>
        <category>Illustrator</category>
        <category>Architect</category>
        <category>Symfony</category>
        <category>Management</category>
        <category>QA</category>
        <category>Embedded</category>
        <category>3D Animation</category>
        <category>Social Media</category>
        <category>Motion Design</category>
        <category>Other non-tech</category>
        <category>CTO</category>
        <category>Marketing Analyst</category>
        <category>Fullstack</category>
        <category>Marketing</category>
        <category>.NET</category>
        <category>Penetration Tester</category>
        <category>Data Analytics</category>
        <category>Game Design</category>
        <category>Operations</category>
        <category>Scrum Master</category>
        <category>Data Engineer</category>
        <category>Drupal</category>
        <category>QA Automation</category>
        <category>Recruiter</category>
        <category>Media Buying</category>
        <category>Magento</category>
        <category>2D Animation</category>
        <category>Game Developer</category>
        <category>C Lang</category>
        <category>Leadership</category>
        <category>Graphic Design</category>
        <category>Security</category>
        <category>Technical Writing</category>
        <category>Rust</category>
        <category>Python</category>
        <category>Ruby</category>
        <category>Project Manager</category>
        <category>Affiliate Manager</category>
        <category>Other tech</category>
        <category>JavaScript</category>
        <category>3D Artist</category>
        <category>iOS</category>
        <category>Delivery Manager</category>
        <category>Node.js</category>
        <category>PHP</category>
        <category>Video Editor</category>
        <category>Security Analyst</category>
        <category>Data Science</category>
        <category>Lead</category>
        <category>WordPress</category>
        <category>Product Design</category>
        <category>Artist</category>
        <category>Marketing and Sales</category>
        <category>Information Security</category>
        <category>Data Analyst</category>
        <category>CIO</category>
        <category>Vue.js</category>
        <category>Laravel</category>
        <category>SQL</category>
        <category>Design</category>
        <category>Advertising</category>
        <category>CEO</category>
        <category>Finances</category>
        <category>SAP</category>
        <category>Odoo</category>
        <category>PPC</category>
        <category>Elixir</category>
        <category>CSO</category>
        <category>Sysadmin</category>
        <category>Flutter</category>
        <category>Unreal Developer</category>
        <category>Golang</category>
        <category>Kotlin</category>
        <category>Unity Developer</category>
        <category>Creative and Gaming</category>
        <category>Content Marketing</category>
        <category>Salesforce</category>
        <category>Quality Assurance</category>
        <category>Sales</category>
        <category>Level Design</category>
        <category>React Native</category>
        <category>Interviewer</category>
        <category>CPP</category>
        <category>COO</category>
        <category>Unity</category>
        <category>Angular</category>
        <category>MS Dynamics</category>
        <category>VFX Artist</category>
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        <category>Head Chief</category>
        <category>Java</category>
        <category>Content Design</category>
        <category>C++</category>
        <category>HR</category>
        <category>SEO</category>
        <category>Support</category>
        <category>ML AI</category>
        <category>Talent Acquisition</category>
        <category>Scala</category>
        <category>Development</category>
        <category>Product Manager</category>
        <category>CPO</category>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:48:05 +0300</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title>Scala Team Lead</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/647009-scala-team-lead/</link>
            <description>VeliTech is a product company where everyone is passionate about technology and strives to stay
                ahead of the curve. Our team is fueled by a deep understanding of cutting-edge frameworks, technologies,
                and continuous learning.

                This combo brought us success: 35+ million users served with our iGaming products, breakthrough Tech
                Radar, and a team of 200+ bright minds who made this happen.

                And this team is ready to welcome you into a world of opportunities to grow and expand your expertise.

                If this piques your interest, then look no further – this is the perfect opportunity for you!

                We invite the Scala Team Lead to join the VeliHorizon product team.

                Horizon is an API-driven, microservices-based platform that takes online casinos, sports betting, and
                other related services to the next level.

                Our cutting-edge technology integrates with leading gaming providers for a highly secure, compliant
                gaming environment that's designed to meet all clients' needs.

                Tech stack:
                Scala 2/3, Typed Akka, ZIO, PostgreSQL, Elasticsearch, Clickhouse, K8s, Kafka, gRPC, AWS

                In this role, you will:
                - hands-on contribution and leadership of team feature development, delivery and supervising in quality
                assurance;
                - lead code, application and architecture design review, improvements and R&amp;D activities;
                - lead and participate in SRE practice, housekeeping, on-call, correction-of-errors, continuous
                improvement process and practice in a team;
                - participate in cross-functional activities and collective leadership processes Team Lead Catch Up,
                Scala Community and Technical Board;
                - maintenance and effective legacy replacement of Spring-Boot / Java + Akka 2.5 / Scala 2.12 based
                service to modern Scala 2.13, Akka 2.6 / Scala 2 and 3 + ZIO 2 stacks".

                Skills and experience you will need:
                - Solid experience with Scala/Akka(Stream, Cluster, Persistence, gRPC, Kafka) stack to develop online
                transaction processing services;
                - Experience with Kafka, PostgreSQL;
                - Deep understanding of functional and object-oriented programming concepts and design patterns;
                - Understanding of microservices-based and event-driven architecture;
                - Ability to write clean, concise and maintainable code.

                Will be a big plus:
                - Experience with JDK upgrade and GC tuning (shenandoah, g1, zero gc, cms, parallel);
                - Experience with K8s application troubleshooting and resource tuning;
                - Experience with Elasticsearch, Redis, DynamoDB;
                - Experience with Tapir, gRPC, Scala 3, ZIO, cats;
                - Experience with Java;
                - Experience of work in a product company with real production application;
                - Experience of work with DevOps/SRE/XP software development practice;
                -Experience in PostgreSQL Database query optimization.

                We offer:
                Health care
                - Medical insurance - full coverage;
                - Paid sick days - 10 days;
                - Well-being program.

                Well-deserved rest
                - Paid vacation - 20 days.

                Work-from-anywhere opportunities
                - Home;
                - Office;
                - Mix both options the way you want.

                Learning and Development
                - Possibility to visit conferences and professional events;
                - Internal educational programs;
                - Certification opportunities.

                Lifestyle
                - Product mindset;
                - Engineering culture in our DNA;
                - T-shaped skill set model.
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:48:05 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/647009-scala-team-lead/</guid>
            <category>Scala</category>
            <category/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Server Engineer</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/646575-server-engineer/</link>
            <description>**Job Description**
                - Work on scalable solutions using event-driven architecture and Domain-Driven Design (DDD)
                - Responsible for the entire lifecycle of feature development, from initial discussions with product
                teams, defining requirements, APIs and providing estimates, to actual coding in collaboration with the
                team, monitoring performance, and delivering robust solutions to end-users
                - Advocate and present chosen architectures to the team, playing an active role in the evolution of our
                tech stack
                - Optimizing system performance, reliability, and stability, making sure our service remains seamless
                and accessible
                - Proactively participate in technical discussions to improve existing architecture and developer
                experience
                **Qualifications:**
                - An experienced Server Engineer with a minimum of 5 years in the field, with a concentration on JVM
                stack and/or TypeScript; functional languages experience is a plus (Scala , Kotlin, etc )
                - Experience with SQL/NoSQL solutions and basic DB architectures, hands on with composing and profiling
                queries
                - Experience in designing server solutions, API design and handling technical discussions
                - Experience in writing unit and integration tests, understanding of TDD concept
                - Familiarity with proto-based APIs and understanding of Kafka or similar messaging systems
                - Familiarity with cloud solutions, microservice orchestration tools and architecture experience
                (Docker, K8s, load balancing concepts, Nginx)
                Superb debug/re-factoring skills
                - Passion for product development and ability to take ownership over full development lifecycle
                - Flexibility to work occasional untraditional hours if required for on-call duty
                **About the team**
                We are a part of the eCommerce platform group. Our mission is to create a robust, reliable and scalable
                platform for internal and external clients—be it individual entrepreneurs, another Wix vertical or large
                agency, and become an open platform to run any eComm business. As part of this goal our team, along with
                other domains, strives to provide APIs, SPIs, and tools to handle, extend and customize multiple
                business workflows, to answer as many use-cases as possible. It is done in a generic, easy to use way,
                and aims to meet the developers standards and industry known methods.
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:21:31 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/646575-server-engineer/</guid>
            <category>Scala</category>
            <category>Java</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Senior BigData Developer</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/646563-senior-bigdata-developer/</link>
            <description>**Project Description:**
                During the 2008 financial crisis, many big banks failed or faced issues due to liquidity issues. Lack of
                liquidity can kill any financial institution over the night. That's why it's so critical to constantly
                monitor liquidity risks and properly maintain collaterals.
                We are looking for a number of talented developers, who would like to join our team in Pune, which is
                building liquidity risk and collateral management platform for one of the biggest investment banks over
                the globe. The platform is a set of front-end tools and back-end engines. Our platform helps the bank to
                increase efficiency and scalability, reduce operational risk and eliminate the majority of manual
                interventions in processing margin calls.
                Responsibilities:The candidate will work on development of new functionality for Liqudity Risk platform
                closely with other teams over the globe.
                **Mandatory Skills Description:**
                - BigData experience (6 years+);
                - Java/python J2EE, Spark, Hive;
                - SQL Databases; UNIX Shell;
                - Strong Experience in Apache Hadoop, Spark, Hive, Impala, Yarn, Talend, Hue;
                - Big Data Reporting, Querying and analysis.

                **Nice-to-Have Skills:**
                - Apache Hadoop, Spark, Hive, Impala, Yarn, Talend, Hue
                - Spark Calculators based on business logic/rules
                - Basic performance tuning and troubleshooting knowledge
                - Experience with all aspects of the SDLC
                - Experience with complex deployment infrastructures
                - Knowledge in software architecture, design and testing
                - Data flow automation (Apache NiFi, Airflow etc)
                - Understanding of difference between OOP and Functional design approach
                - Understanding of an event driven architecture
                - Spring, Maven, GIT, uDeploy;
                **Languages:**
                English: B2 Upper Intermediate
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:28:49 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/646563-senior-bigdata-developer/</guid>
            <category>Scala</category>
            <category/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Senior BigData Developer</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/646361-senior-bigdata-developer/</link>
            <description>Project Description:
                During the 2008 financial crisis, many big banks failed or faced issues due to liquidity issues. Lack of
                liquidity can kill any financial institution over the night. That's why it's so critical to constantly
                monitor liquidity risks and properly maintain collaterals.
                We are looking for a number of talented developers, who would like to join our team in Pune, which is
                building liquidity risk and collateral management platform for one of the biggest investment banks over
                the globe. The platform is a set of front-end tools and back-end engines. Our platform helps the bank to
                increase efficiency and scalability, reduce operational risk and eliminate the majority of manual
                interventions in processing margin calls.

                Responsibilities:
                The candidate will work on development of new functionality for Liqudity Risk platform closely with
                other teams over the globe.

                Mandatory Skills Description:
                - BigData experience (4 years+);
                - Scala, Spark, Hive
                - SQL Databases; UNIX Shell;
                - BigData (understand MapReduce), HDFS, Yarn;

                Nice-to-Have Skills:
                - Java
                - Apache Hadoop, Spark, Hive, Impala, Yarn, Talend, Hue
                - Spark Calculators based on business logic/rules
                - Basic performance tuning and troubleshooting knowledge
                - Experience with all aspects of the SDLC
                - Experience with complex deployment infrastructures
                - Knowledge in software architecture, design and testing
                - Data flow automation (Apache NiFi, Airflow etc)
                - Understanding of difference between OOP and Functional design approach
                - Understanding of an event driven architecture
                - Spring, Maven, GIT, uDeploy;

                Languages:
                English: B2 Upper Intermediate
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:55:27 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/646361-senior-bigdata-developer/</guid>
            <category>SQL</category>
            <category>Scala</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Senior Scala (with Spark) Developer IRC220318</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/645687-senior-scala-with-spark-developer-irc220318/</link>
            <description>**Description:**
                Our client is one of the United States’ largest high-speed Internet, video and phone providers to
                residential customers.
                We’re looking for a dedicated and passionate Sr. Engineer to join our cloud networking team. If you have
                experience building scalable, cloud based, web applications, are excited about impacting millions of
                users, look no further!
                We are building a large scale and high performance cloud based networking service platform that will
                deliver the next generation of Internet services across private and public networks.

                **Requirements:**
                #Required:

                5+ years experience with high-scale, high performance and high-availability server development in Scala.
                Expertise in large-scale data processing and transformation using Spark.
                Understanding of distributed computing principles and the ability to design scalable data pipelines.
                Experience with ETL processes and tools for data extraction, transformation, and loading.
                Proficiency in handling real-time streaming data and processing with Spark Streaming.
                Experience with cloud platforms (AWS is preferable) for deploying and running Spark applications.
                Solid understanding of algorithm complexity, parallel/distributed systems, advanced data structures,
                computer networking, and operating systems.
                Development expertise in REST/SOAP/JSON API
                Development expertise in message bus technologies such as RabbitMQ, ActiveMQ; Apache Kafka
                Solid working knowledge of NoSQL – Cassandra, MongoDB
                #Prefered:

                Prior experience working with Agile/Scrum methodologies
                Start-up environment experience
                Bachelor’s degree in computer science or related field. Master’s preferred

                **Responsibilities:**
                As a Sr. Software Engineer, you will specialize in building high-performance, reliable back-end systems
                and server-side APIs, creating the interconnectivity fabric of the platform and enabling the
                provisioning of a new and revolutionary class of services to millions of Internet users.

                • Design and develop REST and messaging based software infrastructure and build back-end systems and
                APIs
                • Design and develop low latency/high throughput server infrastructure components to handle large volume
                of transactions
                • Analyze requirements, design and develop code, unit test code and test tools
                • Present and defend architectural, design, and technical choices to internal and external audiences.
                • Comfortable with collaboration, open communication and reaching across dev, qa, ops and other cross
                functional teams
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 14:23:47 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/645687-senior-scala-with-spark-developer-irc220318/</guid>
            <category>Scala</category>
            <category/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Scala Team Lead</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/645600-scala-team-lead/</link>
            <description>VeliTech is a product company, where everyone is passionate about technology and strives to
                stay ahead of the curve. Our team is fueled by a deep understanding of cutting-edge frameworks,
                technologies, and continuous learning.

                This combo brought us success, 35+ million users served with our iGaming products, breakthrough Tech
                Radar, and a team of 200+ bright minds who made this happen.

                And this team is ready to welcome you in a world of opportunities to grow and expand your expertise.

                If this piques your interest, then look no further – this is the perfect opportunity for you!

                **We invite Scala Team Lead to join VeliHorizon product team.**

                Horizon is the API-driven, microservices-based platform that takes online casinos, sports betting, and
                beyond to the next level.

                Our cutting-edge technology integrates with leading gaming providers for a highly-secured, compliant
                gaming environment that's designed to meet all clients' needs.

                **Tech stack:**
                Scala 2/3, Typed Akka, ZIO, PostgreSQL, Elasticsearch, Clickhouse, K8s, Kafka, gRPC, AWS

                **In this role, you will:**
                -hands-on contribution and leadership of team feature development, delivery and supervising in quality
                assurance;
                -lead code, application and architecture design review, improvements and R&amp;D activities;
                -lead and participate in SRE practice, housekeeping, on-call, correction-of-errors, continuous
                improvement process and practice in a team;
                -participate in cross-functional activities and collective leadership processes Team Lead Catch Up,
                Scala Community and Technical Board;
                -maintenance and effective legacy replacement of Spring-Boot / Java + Akka 2.5 / Scala 2.12 based
                service to modern Scala 2.13, Akka 2.6 / Scala 2 and 3 + ZIO 2 stacks".

                **Skills and experience you will need:**
                -Solid experience with Scala/Akka(Stream, Cluster, Persistence, gRPC, Kafka) stack to develop online
                transaction processing services;
                -Experience with Kafka, PostgreSQL;
                -Deep understanding of functional and object-oriented programming concepts and design patterns;
                -Understanding of microservices-based and event-driven architecture;
                -Ability to write clean, concise and maintainable code.

                **Will be a big plus:**
                -Experience with JDK upgrade and GC tuning(shenandoah, g1, zero gc, cms, parallel);
                -Experience with K8s application troubleshooting and resource tuning;
                -Experience with Elasticsearch, Redis, DynamoDB;
                -Experience with Tapir, gRPC, Scala 3, ZIO, cats;
                -Experience with Java;
                -Experience of work in a product company with real production application;
                -Experience of work with DevOps/SRE/XP software development practise;
                -Experience of PostgreSQL Database query optimization.

                **We offer:**
                **Health care**
                -Medical insurance - full coverage;
                -Paid sick days - 10 days;
                -Well-being program.

                **Well-deserved rest**
                -Paid vacation - 20 days.

                **Work-from-anywhere opportunities**
                -Home;
                -Office;
                -Mix both options the way you want.

                **Learning and Development**
                -Budget for self-education (hard and soft skills);
                -Possibility to visit conferences and professional events;
                -English language courses + speaking club;
                -Internal educational programs;
                -Certification opportunities.

                **Lifestyle**
                -Product mindset;
                -Engineering culture in our DNA;
                -T-shaped skill set model.
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:48:21 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/645600-scala-team-lead/</guid>
            <category>Scala</category>
            <category/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Senior Scala/Spark Software Engineer (Data Science team) IRC216702</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/637265-senior-scala-spark-software-engineer-data-sci/</link>
            <description>Description:
                Founded in 2007, Rubicon Project’s pioneering technology created a new model for the advertising
                industry. Today, our automated advertising platform is used by the world’s leading publishers and
                applications to transact with top brands around the globe enabling them to reach more than 1 billion
                consumers. Rubicon Project operates the largest independent Display Advertising Exchange and Supply Side
                Platform that automates the buying and selling of Display Advertising across all formats (banner, video)
                on all devices (desktop browsers, mobile devices, billboards). Rubicon Project auctions over 20 Billion
                Ads on a daily basis in real-time in less than 1/2 of a second each. Rubicon Project is a publicly
                traded company (NYSE: RUBI) headquartered in Los Angeles, California, USA.

                Requirements:
                4+ years of production coding experience on the server side;
                Expertise in Scala, Spark;
                Demonstrated strong English language verbal and written communication skills (at least intermediate
                level by client request);
                Expertise in Service-oriented architectures, microservices, advanced database schemas, relational and
                nonrelational databases, and highly scalable and available web services;
                Readiness to work on different types of projects from POC &amp; MVP with based on very high-level
                requirements to production-ready. Work will include very close collaboration with the Data Science team;
                Familiarity with HTTP protocol, networking, CDN, and Web performance factors;
                A strong understanding of algorithms, and data structures, and an ability to recognize the business and
                technical trade-offs between different solutions;
                Experience with development and CI tools: maven, git, Jenkins, Puppet, Crucible, Jira;
                Experience working in a Linux environment;
                Expertise in building software in an agile development environment.

                Responsibilities:
                Be a creative problem-solver who can draw on an array of expertise and technology to design and
                implement reliable, scalable and maintainable solutions to challenging problems;
                Write production-ready code and unit tests that meet both system and business requirements;
                Design software and prepare technical specifications;
                Respond to feature requests, bug reports, performance issues and ad-hoc questions;
                Work collaboratively with multiple teams to deliver quality software;
                Perform code reviews and design reviews.
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:42:25 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/637265-senior-scala-spark-software-engineer-data-sci/</guid>
            <category>Scala</category>
            <category/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Senior Big Data Developer</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/617654-senior-big-data-developer/</link>
            <description>**This is an opportunity to work with the world’s most valuable company, whose mission is to
                bring the best user experience to its customers through its innovative hardware, software, and
                services.**

                **Requirements:**

                - Proven experience in crafting, implementing and supporting highly scalable data systems and services
                in Scala and Java
                - Solid experience with Apache Spark and Streaming
                - Proven skills in designing scalable, highly available distributed systems using Kubernetes
                - Data processing experience at scale
                - Streaming experience at scale
                - Strong communication skills and ability to work closely with and collaboratively with others
                - Able to capture cross-functional requirements and translate them into practical engineering tasks
                - You will need to have a real passion for quality and an ability to understand complex systems

                **Responsibilities:**
                - This is your opportunity to help engineer highly visible global-scale systems with petabytes of data,
                supporting hundreds of millions of users
                - This role includes elements both of ad hoc analysis as well as roll up of production grade data feeds
                - This role also includes an essential thread of data privacy and security
                - This is a rare opportunity to join a focused team and work collaboratively with other groups to make a
                significant impact
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:54:01 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/617654-senior-big-data-developer/</guid>
            <category>Scala</category>
            <category/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Senior Java with Big data</title>
            <link>https://djinni.co/jobs/639597-senior-java-with-big-data/</link>
            <description>**Project Description:**

                Embark on a transformative journey with our revolutionary cross-asset data management platform, designed
                to redefine the landscape of global finance. Our next-generation platform stands at the forefront of
                innovation, meticulously crafted to deliver globally consistent data and pioneering tools. Aimed at
                empowering trade and sales clients, this platform is the cornerstone for executing business strategies
                with precision and agility.

                Built upon a robust big data architecture, our platform is not only highly scalable but also primed for
                the cloud era. It serves as the bedrock for industry-leading analytics, offering unparalleled client
                reporting, regulatory compliance, and a suite of solutions for surveillance, supervisory reporting, and
                data science, affectionately known as "data flame." Our project leverages a sophisticated tech stack
                comprising Java, Scala, Spring, SQL, Kafka, and Hadoop, setting a new standard for excellence.

                **Opportunity:**

                We are in search of an exceptional Senior Java Developer, someone who embodies leadership, innovation,
                and technical prowess. The ideal candidate is not just a developer but a visionary, capable of working
                synergistically within a team, mentoring peers, engaging stakeholders, and taking full accountability
                for the team's outputs and the success of assigned activities.

                As the Tech Lead, you will be at the helm of a dynamic development team, comprising 2 Senior and 2
                Regular Java Developers. This role is a rare opportunity to delve deep into the realm of big data within
                the prestigious environment of an international bank, enhancing your expertise and shaping the future of
                financial data management.

                **Responsibilities:**

                - Analyze and transition from existing systems to our cutting-edge solution.
                - Architect and design the blueprint of the new platform.
                - Develop components to support existing functionalities and new business demands.
                - Optimize for scalability and performance.
                - Integrate with a variety of external data sources including Storm, JDBC, KDB+, websockets, REST
                services, and flat files.
                - Lead and manage a high-caliber team to success.

                **Mandatory Skills:**

                - At least 1 year of Big Data development experience, with hands-on expertise in Spark programming.
                - Comprehensive development skills, including:
                - API design and construction in Java;
                - Java server-side or back-end development;
                - Mastery of Core Java, Java collections, and multithreading;
                - Java Memory Management;
                - Advanced SQL knowledge.
                - A deep understanding of distributed systems and CI/CD workflows.
                - Proficiency in Linux.
                - Exceptional problem-solving capabilities.
                - A proactive, enthusiastic attitude with a keenness to learn and adapt.

                **Nice-to-Have Skills:**

                - Proficiency in Apache Spark and in-memory databases.
                - Experience with the Hadoop ecosystem.
                - Financial sector experience.
                - Over 1 year of Machine Learning experience, in Java or Python.

                **Language Requirements:**

                - English: B2 Upper Intermediate

                Join us in this ambitious project to forge the future of financial data management, leveraging
                cutting-edge technology to drive innovation and excellence. Your journey with us will be one of
                challenge, growth, and unparalleled opportunity.
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:33:27 +0300</pubDate>
            <guid>https://djinni.co/jobs/639597-senior-java-with-big-data/</guid>
            <category>Java</category>
            <category>Scala</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
